<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>computing technology blog -stackoverflow - Google Blog Search</title>
    <link>https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=computing+technology+blog+-stackoverflow&amp;client=firefox-a&amp;hs=HpG&amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;tbm=blg&amp;tbs=qdr:d,lr:lang_1en</link>
    <description>About 1,930 results</description>
    <opensearch:totalResults>1930</opensearch:totalResults>
    <opensearch:startIndex>1</opensearch:startIndex>
    <opensearch:itemsPerPage>10</opensearch:itemsPerPage>
    <item>
      <title>Other World &lt;b&gt;Computing&lt;/b&gt; Named Green Tech Company of the Year &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://blog.macsales.com/21371-other-world-computing-named-green-tech-company-of-the-year-by-business-intelligence-group-for-corporate-environmental-protection-efforts</link>
      <description>OWC &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; - &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt;.macsales.com &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; “It&amp;#39;s an honor to receive this recognition for our environmental efforts,” said Larry O&amp;#39;Connor, founder and CEO of Other World &lt;em&gt;Computing&lt;/em&gt;. “Just as our corporate mission is to provide our customers the resources they need to maximize their &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt; investment, we see our environmental mission as maximizing available &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt; to conserve natural resources while providing the highest level of operational efficiency. It&amp;#39;s a win for everybody.”.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Other World Computing Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>OWC NewsFeed</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 22:00:43 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts after my week at AWS re:Invent 2013 &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; - the Radware &lt;b&gt;Blog&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://blog.radware.com/events/2013/11/thoughts-after-my-week-at-aws-reinvent-2013-conference/</link>
      <description>Not only was I able to attend one of the largest events for cloud &lt;em&gt;computing&lt;/em&gt;, but I also learned about innovative &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt; powering the AWS eco-system, I met great people such as AWS customers, AWS partners and AWS personnel.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Radware Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Lior Cohen</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 09:24:28 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWC DIY Data Doubler Kits: Versatility Limited Only by Creativity</title>
      <link>http://blog.macsales.com/21376-owc-diy-data-doubler-kits-versatility-limited-only-by-creativity</link>
      <description>Time Machine was created as a “set it and forget it” &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt; to help people back up their data. The catch is that in order to back up your data, it has to be plugged into your &lt;em&gt;computer&lt;/em&gt;. Even the most vigilant laptop owner could forget to do that&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Other World Computing Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>OWC Mason</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 18:00:16 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMware End User &lt;b&gt;Computing&lt;/b&gt;: Horizon View 5.3 Storage &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.insidetheregistry.com/blog/2013/11/22/vmware-end-user-computing-horizon-view-5-3-storage-optimization-features-deep-dive/</link>
      <description>NOTE: This is syndicated content from The VMware &lt;em&gt;Blogs&lt;/em&gt; and as such any views or opinions presented are solely those of the respective author(s) and do not necessarily represent those of insidetheregistry.com or the site authors. Copyright of this content &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; This feature is beneficial to customers who use third-party storage &lt;em&gt;technologies&lt;/em&gt; (for example, Atlantis &lt;em&gt;Computing&lt;/em&gt; VSA), which optimize the space consumed by the virtual disks of the individual virtual machines. Note: When the&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Technology Musings Including Microsoft, Citrix and VMware...</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>The VMware Blogs</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 06:34:55 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud &lt;b&gt;Computing&lt;/b&gt; is a sustaining innovation and some of its &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://khalafalla.wordpress.com/2013/11/22/cloud-computing-is-a-sustaining-innovation-and-some-of-its-applications-are-a-disruptive-innovations/</link>
      <description>مدونة خلف الله الخير Khalafalla Elkheir&amp;#39;s &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; &amp;middot; &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; &amp;middot; About &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Tags: Clayton M. Christensen, Cloud &lt;em&gt;Computing&lt;/em&gt;, disruptive innovation, Disruptive &lt;em&gt;Technologies&lt;/em&gt;, disruptive &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt;, sustaining innovation. Cloud &lt;em&gt;Computing&lt;/em&gt; the current hype&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>مدونة خلف الله الخير Khalafalla Elkheir's Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>khalafalla</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 10:20:06 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel&amp;#39;s Recovery Realization - Bits &lt;b&gt;Blog&lt;/b&gt; - The New York Times</title>
      <link>http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/11/21/intels-recovery-realization/</link>
      <description>Intel executives made a startling admission: that the company&amp;#39;s fixation on personal &lt;em&gt;computers&lt;/em&gt; blinded it to the reality that transistors are getting more dense and &lt;em&gt;computing&lt;/em&gt; intelligence is traveling to ever-smaller things. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; In the temple of &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt;, Intel has confessed to straying from the true path. That may prove to be the start of salvation for the company, the world&amp;#39;s largest maker of semiconductors, but at a price that is yet to be known. Thursday&amp;#39;s annual meeting for Wall Street&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>NYT Bits</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>By QUENTIN HARDY</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 04:10:58 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paying to attract more CS teachers in England | &lt;b&gt;Computing&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://computinged.wordpress.com/2013/11/22/paying-to-attract-more-cs-teachers-in-england/</link>
      <description>Bursaries will be available to top graduates in maths, physics, chemistry, &lt;em&gt;computing&lt;/em&gt;, and languages, in primary and in priority subjects at secondary school (English, history, biology, geography, music, and design and &lt;em&gt;technology&lt;/em&gt;). via Bigger bursaries and scholarships to attract more top graduates into teaching – Press releases &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Related. Entry filed under: Uncategorized. Tags: &lt;em&gt;computing&lt;/em&gt; education, public policy, teachers. What Sir Ken Got Wrong, and what the &lt;em&gt;blogger&lt;/em&gt; got wrong too&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Computing Education Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Mark Guzdial</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 06:43:21 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact Of Web Services And Cloud &lt;b&gt;Computing&lt;/b&gt; Information &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.ukessays.com/essays/information-technology/impact-of-web-services-and-cloud-computing-information-technology-essay.php</link>
      <description>Since &lt;em&gt;computing technology&lt;/em&gt; started playing a significant role in commerce and industry, business organisations continually face a challenge of having to ... &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; A &lt;em&gt;blogger&lt;/em&gt; can make money from &lt;em&gt;blogging&lt;/em&gt; my advertising on his &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; page.</description>
      <dc:publisher>RSS Feed for UK Essays</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>unknown</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 15:28:06 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud &lt;b&gt;computing&lt;/b&gt; beats Moore&amp;#39;s law — by a mile | VentureBeat</title>
      <link>http://venturebeat.com/2013/11/21/cloud-computing-beats-moores-law-by-a-mile/</link>
      <description>Open source &lt;em&gt;technologies&lt;/em&gt; such as Linux, Java, MySQL, MongoDB, PHP, Node.js and countless others are the building blocks and the basic plumbing for those who want to turn ideas into products — fast and cheap. The cloud is not just about handling any workload you can throw at it. It&amp;#39;s about connecting the great &lt;em&gt;technologies&lt;/em&gt; you &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Topics: cloud &lt;em&gt;computing&lt;/em&gt;, Gianugo Rabellino, Microsoft, microsoft open &lt;em&gt;technologies&lt;/em&gt;, Moore&amp;#39;s Law &amp;middot; &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; comments powered by Disqus. Advertise on&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>VentureBeat</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Gianugo Rabellino / Microsoft Open Technologies</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 21 Nov 2013 15:20:30 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horizon View 5.3 Storage Optimization Features &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; - VMware &lt;b&gt;Blogs&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://blogs.vmware.com/euc/2013/11/vmware-horizon-view-5-3-storage-optimization-features-deep-dive.html</link>
      <description>This feature is beneficial to customers who use third-party storage &lt;em&gt;technologies&lt;/em&gt; (for example, Atlantis &lt;em&gt;Computing&lt;/em&gt; VSA), which optimize the space consumed by the virtual disks of the individual virtual machines. Note: When the Unbounded&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>VMware End-User Computing Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Tina de Benedictis</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 06:34:55 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>