<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>software best practice -stackoverflow - Google Blog Search</title>
    <link>https://www.google.co.uk/search?client=firefox-a&amp;hs=EbG&amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;q=software+best+practice+-stackoverflow&amp;tbm=blg&amp;tbs=qdr:d,lr:lang_1en</link>
    <description>About 1,080 results</description>
    <opensearch:totalResults>1080</opensearch:totalResults>
    <opensearch:startIndex>1</opensearch:startIndex>
    <opensearch:itemsPerPage>10</opensearch:itemsPerPage>
    <item>
      <title>My thoughts on eHealth | Train It Medical</title>
      <link>http://trainitmedical.com.au/my-thoughts-on-ehealth</link>
      <description>Ms Otto has trained hundreds of doctors in not only using clinical &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt; like Medical Director and &lt;em&gt;Best Practice&lt;/em&gt; but all aspects of eHealth, including secure messaging, ePrescribing, clinical coding and database cleansing, as well as the&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Train It Medical</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Train IT Medical</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 04:08:54 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JDA &lt;b&gt;Software&lt;/b&gt; Group, Inc.</title>
      <link>http://www.jda.com/</link>
      <description>Supply chain management &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt; and services from JDA &lt;em&gt;Software&lt;/em&gt; is used globally by more than 3200 companies worldwide to solve their toughest business challenges. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Best Practices&lt;/em&gt; in Transportation Procurement &amp;middot; The Role of&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>SmartTurn Forums and Blogs - Blogs - SmartTurn Inventory and Warehouse Management Best Practices Series by Kevin Collins</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Kevin Collins</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 09:58:55 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatar National Library organises 8th Annual MENA Innovative Users &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.qatarisbooming.com/2013/11/24/qatar-national-library-organises-8th-annual-mena-innovative-users-group-conference/</link>
      <description>MENA information and library professionals gathered to attend the two-day &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt; technical conference at Georgetown Universty in Qatar (GU-Q) to learn about emerging library technologies and trends, explore a wide range of library products &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; conference was an incredible opportunity for the MENA information and library professionals to share ideas, learn more about innovative library technologies, present and review &lt;em&gt;best practice&lt;/em&gt;-implementations, and network with colleagues.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Qatar Business &amp; Corporate News</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Qatar is BooMING</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 14:28:23 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feedback on eLearning Assessments: 5 &lt;b&gt;Best Practices&lt;/b&gt; – An &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://blog.commlabindia.com/elearning/elearning-assessments-feedback-infographic</link>
      <description>Here are some &lt;em&gt;best practices&lt;/em&gt; for giving feedback for assessment questions in eLearning courses. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Assessments: 5 &lt;em&gt;Best Practices&lt;/em&gt; – An Infographic. Feedback on eLearning Assessments: 5 &lt;em&gt;Best Practices&lt;/em&gt; – An Infographic. by Srujan Pakala.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Custom training and elearning, anywhere anytime!</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Srujan Pakala</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 20:30:19 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#39;US government rarely uses &lt;b&gt;best&lt;/b&gt; cybersecurity steps&amp;#39; | Worlds Latest &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://easymoneyrighthere.blogspot.com/2013/11/us-government-rarely-uses-best.html</link>
      <description>The US government itself seldom follows the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; cybersecurity &lt;em&gt;practices&lt;/em&gt; and must drop its old operating systems and unsecured browsers as it tries to push the private sector to tighten its &lt;em&gt;practices&lt;/em&gt;, technology advisers told President Barack Obama. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; The advisers said the government should rely more on automatic updates of &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt;, require better proof of identities of people, devices and &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt;, and more widely use the Trusted Platform Module, an embedded security chip.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Worlds Latest Happenings Live here</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Aruna Rajagiri</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 18:00:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agile Complexification Inverter: 13+2 Sprint Cadence</title>
      <link>http://agilecomplexificationinverter.blogspot.com/2013/11/132-sprint-cadence.html</link>
      <description>What is the &lt;em&gt;best practice&lt;/em&gt; - a funny question. There is no &lt;em&gt;best practice&lt;/em&gt; for sprint length. But what factors &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Perhaps you have heard of the S.O.L.I.D. &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt; design principles of Object Oriented Design, but lack the motivation to practice the prin.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Agile Complexification Inverter</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>David Koontz</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 22:21:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spatial &lt;b&gt;practice&lt;/b&gt; frames harbin twin towers as digital gateway</title>
      <link>http://www.designboom.com/architecture/spatial-practice-frames-harbin-twin-towers-as-digital-gateway-11-24-2013/</link>
      <description>performing as a digital gateway, for the haxi district in china, the &amp;#39;harbin twin towers&amp;#39; by chinese studio spatial &lt;em&gt;practice&lt;/em&gt; frame the city and station. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; all images courtesy of spatial &lt;em&gt;practice&lt;/em&gt; &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; the adjacent plaza, facilitating connections between travelers, commuters and residents. contrasting elements within the structure balance between empty and full, mass and void, private and public spaces. the &lt;em&gt;programs&lt;/em&gt; of each generate a dialogue with the site – the north soho and service apartment&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>designboom | architecture &amp; design magazine</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>spatial</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 01:19:23 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The IT triangle strategy for evaluating enterprise tech startups &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://gigaom.com/2013/11/23/the-it-triangle-strategy-for-evaluating-enterprise-tech-startups/</link>
      <description>There have been plenty of blog posts on why enterprise startups are “hot,” but enterprise startups can range from cloud infrastructure companies to developer &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt; to new enterprise applications. Evaluating each market is very different because each of these markets are built upon each other (e.g., &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; Jerry Chen is a partner at Greylock Partners and former vice president at VMware. Upcoming: Security and Compliance &lt;em&gt;Best Practices&lt;/em&gt; for SaaS Companies, Dec. 3, 10 AM PST.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Gigaom</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Jerry Chen</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 20:00:37 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gelogical Professionals Job, Frontline Exploration Production Job &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.jobinpk.com/gelogical-professionals-job-frontline-exploration-production-job-geophysical-professionals-24-november/</link>
      <description>Good understanding of Interpretation &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt; (Petrel and Geographic) will be preferred. SENIOR &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Have thorough understanding of data cloaning and loading procedures along with QC methodolog.es and &lt;em&gt;best practices&lt;/em&gt;. • Have good&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Newspaper Job ads, Jobs in Pakistan, Bank Jobs, Sindh Punjab Jobs Karachi</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Tanha Karim</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 10:14:18 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMMI Institute to Help Companies around the World Elevate &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.emiratesweek.com/2013/11/46704</link>
      <description>The CMMI Institute, established by Carnegie Mellon University, is home to the Capability Maturity Model Integration (CMMI), a gold standard of excellence in &lt;em&gt;software&lt;/em&gt; and systems development. The Institute will continue to help this &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; company regardless of size or industry. KK Raman, Partner Business Excellence, KPMG India says, “Carnegie Mellon is a pioneer in developing &lt;em&gt;best practices&lt;/em&gt; and transitioning them to industry, and this is reflected in the global adoption of the CMMI.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Emirates Week</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>ME NewsWire</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 11:12:58 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>