<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>developer productivity blog -stackoverflow -"real estate" - Google Blog Search</title>
    <link>https://www.google.co.uk/search?lr=lang_en&amp;q=developer+productivity+blog+-stackoverflow+-%22real+estate%22&amp;client=firefox-a&amp;hs=PdG&amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;tbm=blg&amp;tbs=qdr:d,lr:lang_1en</link>
    <description>About 90 results</description>
    <opensearch:totalResults>90</opensearch:totalResults>
    <opensearch:startIndex>1</opensearch:startIndex>
    <opensearch:itemsPerPage>10</opensearch:itemsPerPage>
    <item>
      <title>5 Best Practice Mentalities to Get Over - David Walsh</title>
      <link>http://davidwalsh.name/get-over</link>
      <description>These best practices usually keep us out of trouble but some of them are taken way too literally, to the point where &lt;em&gt;developers&lt;/em&gt; become too rigid and borderline crippled by them. Truth be told &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; No longer did you write globally available functions to modify instances of String, Number, Array, Object, Function, etc -- you could pin methods on the prototype for each so that every existing and future instance had those methods; a total boost to &lt;em&gt;productivity&lt;/em&gt; and code efficiency. Then after a few&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>David Walsh Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>David Walsh</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 14:26:30 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB makes AWS easier | #reinvent | SiliconANGLE</title>
      <link>http://siliconangle.com/blog/2013/12/04/aws-reinvent-2013-mongodb-makes-it-easier-reinvent/</link>
      <description>According to Horowitz, their break-out was the moment they began working to provide &lt;em&gt;developers&lt;/em&gt; with what they really wanted from purely a &lt;em&gt;productivity&lt;/em&gt; standpoint. “[Mongo] lets [&lt;em&gt;developers&lt;/em&gt;] do all these things pretty easily without reinventing&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>SiliconANGLE</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Alan McStravick</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 13:24:28 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monaco – Visual Studio online | Ambilykk&amp;#39;s &lt;b&gt;Blog&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://ambilykk.com/2013/12/04/monaco-visual-studio-online/</link>
      <description>Microsoft taking another step towards optimizing the &lt;em&gt;developer productivity&lt;/em&gt;. &amp;quot;Monaco&amp;quot;- Visual Studio online is a light weight version of Visual Studio available online. Now, you can develop applications using Visual Studio from anywhere and&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Ambilykk's Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>ambilykk</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 06:38:09 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>82 More Tweetable Quotes for Authors | Author Media</title>
      <link>http://www.authormedia.com/82-more-tweetable-quotes-authors/</link>
      <description>Help for authors timid about technology. &lt;em&gt;Blogging&lt;/em&gt; Tips &amp;middot; How To &amp;middot; News &amp;middot; Platform Building Tips &amp;middot; Reviews &amp;middot; Social Media Tips &amp;middot; Website Tips &amp;middot; Writing Tips. You are here: Home &amp;gt; &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; &amp;gt; 82 More Tweetable Quotes for Authors&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Author Media Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Shaney Lee</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 14:00:01 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Productivity&lt;/b&gt; Anywhere – Building Web Apps vs Native Apps</title>
      <link>http://productivityanywhere.com/2013/12/building-web-apps-vs-native-apps/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=building-web-apps-vs-native-apps</link>
      <description>Converting a web app into a mobile app is no easy task, and requires re-thinking all the parts of your service, including data, design, and &lt;em&gt;development&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Reaching an accelerometer can be done as well (http://&lt;em&gt;blogs&lt;/em&gt;.adobe.com/cantrell/archives/ 2012/03/accessing-the-accelerometer-and-gyroscope-in-javascript.html), but this feature isn&amp;#39;t available on a desktop PC for obvious reasons I&amp;#39;ll throw geo-location into the mix, since most native &lt;em&gt;developer&lt;/em&gt; advocates tend to conveniently forget&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Productivity AnywhereProductivity Anywhere</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>derek</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 16:06:56 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 17 Cloud Based IDEs for Web &lt;b&gt;Development&lt;/b&gt; | SiteProNews</title>
      <link>http://www.sitepronews.com/2013/12/04/top-17-cloud-based-ides-web-development/</link>
      <description>Given the growing volume of workloads being done over the cloud, starting from CRM to content sharing to social networking, there is no denying that software or Web &lt;em&gt;development&lt;/em&gt; is moving there, too. Moreover, the rise of &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Its SSH authentication, code compilation and code snippet features help &lt;em&gt;developers&lt;/em&gt; to become more &lt;em&gt;productive&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; He is a geek who developes java applications for Cygnet Infotech and a social media addict, who loves &lt;em&gt;blogging&lt;/em&gt; and tweeting. Connect with him&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>SiteProNews</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Boni Satani</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 05:00:31 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TouchCast Review » 148Apps » iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch App &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.148apps.com/reviews/touchcast-review/</link>
      <description>TouchCast&amp;#39;s obvious want to blur the line between creating and sharing interactive, presentation-quality video is great - for the most part. However, some elements could do with a visual update. &lt;em&gt;Developer&lt;/em&gt;: TouchCast. Price: FREE Version Reviewed: 1.0.5. App Reviewed on: iPad Mini &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; TouchCast is still worth the download if one already happens to be into video-&lt;em&gt;blogging&lt;/em&gt; and the like, and with just a few more updates it could also be great for learning. Posted in: iPad Apps and&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>148Apps - iPhone and iPad App Reviews, Game Reviews, and News</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Arron Hirst</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 17:02:56 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work resumes on new Steilacoom &lt;b&gt;development&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.southpugetsoundnews.com/news/south-puget-sound-government/work-resumes-new-steilacoom-development/</link>
      <description>Heavy machinery is once again running at the Joey Hollow &lt;em&gt;development&lt;/em&gt; in Steilacoom, as a construction crew prepares the site for 17 new homes. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Linda Kent, the Olympic and Southwest Regions Communications Manager for the DOE, told the South Puget Sound News, “High concentrations of particulate matter in water (turbidity) affects light penetration and &lt;em&gt;productivity&lt;/em&gt; and habitat quality. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Subscribe to the &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; and we&amp;#39;ll send you a daily email whenever there is new stories.</description>
      <dc:publisher>South Puget Sound News</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Beth Agnew</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 15:00:27 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Results: Agile &lt;b&gt;Development&lt;/b&gt;: Learning While Working</title>
      <link>http://www.softwareresults.us/2013/12/agile-development-learning-while-working.html</link>
      <description>This tells us that we need to incorporate a principle of lean &lt;em&gt;development&lt;/em&gt; into the mix: We need amplify learning about what we are building and how we are building it, allowing for some overlap between defining and delivering to enable and leverage our learning, as Figure 3-2 illustrates: Figure 3-2. I&amp;#39;m going to fill in the shaded &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; posts will be organized under the “Agile Expectations” content on the left-hand side for easy reference. I welcome your comments and feedback!</description>
      <dc:publisher>Software Results</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>noreply@blogger.com (Dave Moran)</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 01:25:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scala eXchange 2013 Review - Day 1 - NTCoding - London</title>
      <link>http://ntcoding.blogspot.com/2013/12/scala-exchange-2013-review-day-1.html</link>
      <description>Two of the top guys at typesafe presented keynotes which gave us a big insight into where typesafe are focusing their efforts - helping &lt;em&gt;developers&lt;/em&gt; to build concurrent, distributed applications. Scala is about building scalable software, it&amp;#39;s not&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>NTCoding Dev Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Nick (@ntcoding)</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 09:13:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>