<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>developer productivity blog -stackoverflow -"real estate" - Google Blog Search</title>
    <link>https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=developer+productivity+blog+-stackoverflow+-%22real+estate%22&amp;client=firefox-a&amp;hs=PdG&amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;tbm=blg&amp;tbs=qdr:d,lr:lang_1en</link>
    <description>About 117 results</description>
    <opensearch:totalResults>117</opensearch:totalResults>
    <opensearch:startIndex>1</opensearch:startIndex>
    <opensearch:itemsPerPage>10</opensearch:itemsPerPage>
    <item>
      <title>12 days of COBOL - COBOL - &lt;b&gt;Blog&lt;/b&gt; - COBOL - Micro Focus Community</title>
      <link>http://community.microfocus.com/microfocus/cobol/b/weblog/archive/2013/11/28/12daysofcobol.aspx</link>
      <description>Some of the tips will even help you improve your own &lt;em&gt;productivity&lt;/em&gt;! We&amp;#39;ve compiled the list of 12 hints and tips from our Product Management team, our own &lt;em&gt;developers&lt;/em&gt; and more importantly from you - the best source of COBOL knowledge out&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>COBOL - Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Melissa Burns</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 09:00:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frog Draw (&lt;b&gt;Productivity&lt;/b&gt;) | Download Free iOs iPhone and iPad Apps &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://lilyofthevalleycomic.blogspot.com/2013/11/frog-draw-productivity.html</link>
      <description>Category: &lt;em&gt;Productivity&lt;/em&gt; Price: Free, Version: 1.0 (iTunes) Description: Frog Draw is a drawing app for kids. The child can build up freeform pictures by dragging, dropping, pinching, swiping and twisting the provided library of shapes and stickers or from faces imported from your photo library. No ads. Just because it is for kids, doesn&amp;#39;t mean it lacks advanced features. I&amp;#39;m a &lt;em&gt;developer&lt;/em&gt; with decades of pro experience. My current iOS app average 4 stars. This is &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Diberdayakan oleh &lt;em&gt;Blogger&lt;/em&gt; .</description>
      <dc:publisher>Download Free iOs iPhone and iPad Apps Today | Drop Price Today</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>jiha koe</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 07:52:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday Deals for Authors | Author Media</title>
      <link>http://www.authormedia.com/black-friday-2013/</link>
      <description>Buy MyBookTable Professional &amp;middot; Buy MyBookTable &lt;em&gt;Developer&lt;/em&gt;. How to Win &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; So clicking the links not only gives you access to amazing Black Friday deals, it also helps us continue helping authors like you with our free &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; and newsletter.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Author Media Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Thomas Umstattd</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 03:05:36 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW LEASE OF LIFE FOR FORMER LABORATORIES SITE | Kent &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.kentbusinessblog.co.uk/new-lease-of-life-for-former-laboratories-site/</link>
      <description>Demolition is underway of the former Ditton Laboratories, after the two organisations secured planning permission from Tonbridge &amp;amp; Malling Borough Council, to transform the site on Kiln Barn Road, into Orchard Gate, a &lt;em&gt;development&lt;/em&gt; of 37 high &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Millwood&amp;#39;s Deputy Managing Director, said: “This is one of those rare moments where we can play a part in creating a new hamlet set within the heart of the Kent countryside, and at the same time help to ensure the future &lt;em&gt;productivity&lt;/em&gt; of the&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Kent Business News Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Kent Business Blog</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 18:35:19 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newbie &lt;b&gt;Programming&lt;/b&gt; Resources | Toby&amp;#39;s Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://tosbourn.com/2013/11/development/newbie-programming-resources/</link>
      <description>The personal &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; of Toby Osbourn. Menu &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Tonight I asked the internet for recommendations on newbie friendly &lt;em&gt;programming&lt;/em&gt; books and resources, and the internet obliged me with some excellent suggestions :-). I just wanted to record&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Toby's Ramblings</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Toby</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 23:48:32 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Short List Of Sci-Fi Novels Worth Reading | ThoughtStream.new &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://lostechies.com/derickbailey/2013/11/27/a-short-list-of-sci-fi-novels-worth-reading/</link>
      <description>I&amp;#39;ve got a lot of other books that I could talk about in the sci-fi realm (and other realms), but I don&amp;#39;t want to take up too much of the good-will and reputation for &lt;em&gt;developer&lt;/em&gt; and technology &lt;em&gt;blogging&lt;/em&gt; that I&amp;#39;ve built here, if this is something that no one&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Los Techies</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Derick Bailey</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 15:00:33 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearless Giving: The Difference Between a Failed Business &amp;amp; a &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://liveyourlegend.net/fearless-giving-revolutions/</link>
      <description>We met at a &lt;em&gt;blogger&amp;#39;s&lt;/em&gt; meetup in SF, and since then he&amp;#39;s become one of my closer business, tea-drinking and running friends in SF (We somehow even talked ourselves into signing up to run a 50-mile footrace, which we&amp;#39;re taking a crack at in a week from Saturday! &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; It&amp;#39;s why I&amp;#39;ve hired a &lt;em&gt;developer&lt;/em&gt; to create a Connection App so that our community here can easily find each other and connect with other like-minded passionate Living Legends in their hometowns in the real world. We&amp;#39;re&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Live Your Legend</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Scott</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 19:23:55 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Trends: Oil and economy: Understanding the risks [Part 1]</title>
      <link>http://canadiantrends.blogspot.com/2013/11/oil-and-economy-understanding-risks.html</link>
      <description>Guided by this strategy, the Government provides significant resources to support research, &lt;em&gt;development&lt;/em&gt; and technology. It&amp;#39;s not unreasonable to assume the research &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Andrew Leach recently put out a great analysis of pipeline efficiency and the obsession with &amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;productivity&lt;/em&gt;&amp;quot; which provides, in example, an explanation of the paradigm world governments are currently trapped within, deliberately by the banks. The CEPA study is the perfect example of what&amp;#39;s &lt;b&gt;.....&lt;/b&gt; Powered by &lt;em&gt;Blogger&lt;/em&gt;.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Canadian Trends</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Richard</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 21:50:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athos Raises $3.5M in Seed Funding - FinSMEs</title>
      <link>http://www.finsmes.com/2013/11/athos-raises-3-5m-seed-funding.html</link>
      <description>Athos, a Redwood City, CA-based &lt;em&gt;developer&lt;/em&gt; of wearable workout technology that tracks things like muscle &lt;em&gt;productivity&lt;/em&gt;, raised $3.5m in seed funding. The backer was Social+Capital Partnership. The company is using the funds to continue to&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>FinSMEs</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>FinSMEs</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 10:44:35 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it too early? | UDig&amp;#39;s IT Staffing &lt;b&gt;Blog&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.udig.com/blog/2013/11/27/is-it-too-early/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=is-it-too-early</link>
      <description>&lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; &amp;middot; Time Entry &amp;middot; Login &amp;middot; Contact Us &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; deloitte, Dice, digital commerce, Discovery Channel, driverless, droid, Dulles Technology Corridor, dustin wax, earnings, economy, Edwin Jeffords, Elkins Sports Performance, email, emailing, Emily Kittrell , employee retention, employee satisfaction, employee spotlight, employees, employers, employment, end of year, end to end &lt;em&gt;developer&lt;/em&gt;, engineers, enterprise mobile, entertainment industry, entry level, ERE, ere.net, ereader, erlang, etiquette&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>UDig's IT Staffing Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Aaron Snead</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 14:30:14 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>