<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>"computer science" algorithms blog -stackoverflow - Google Blog Search</title>
    <link>https://www.google.co.uk/search?client=firefox-a&amp;hs=RkG&amp;rls=org.mozilla:en-US:official&amp;q=%22computer+science%22+algorithms+blog+-stackoverflow&amp;tbm=blg&amp;tbs=qdr:d,lr:lang_1en</link>
    <description>About 45 results</description>
    <opensearch:totalResults>45</opensearch:totalResults>
    <opensearch:startIndex>1</opensearch:startIndex>
    <opensearch:itemsPerPage>10</opensearch:itemsPerPage>
    <item>
      <title>Event Recap: Social Media News Mining | Tow Center for Digital &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://towcenter.org/blog/event-recap-social-media-news-mining/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; MS Dual Degree: Journalism, &lt;em&gt;Computer Science&lt;/em&gt; &amp;middot; &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; &amp;middot; Latest &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; Posts &amp;middot; Previous &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; Posts &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; 6:30pm for a panel on &lt;em&gt;algorithmic&lt;/em&gt; accountability reporting. Nick Diakopoulos will kick off the evening with research from the Tow Center on the investigation of &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt;, and panelists from journalism, data science, and &lt;em&gt;computer science&lt;/em&gt; will explore the range of what &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt; mean in society, and how journalists might investigate the power that &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt; increasingly exert on us.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Tow Center for Digital Journalism</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Nicholas Diakopoulos</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 15:34:15 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teasing apart the issues of women in computing: Impact of Hollywood</title>
      <link>http://computinged.wordpress.com/2013/11/25/teasing-apart-the-issues-of-women-in-computing/</link>
      <description>A study financed by the Geena Davis Institute on Gender in Media found that recent family films, children&amp;#39;s shows and prime-time programs featured extraordinarily few characters with &lt;em&gt;computer science&lt;/em&gt; or engineering occupations, and… &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Girls Who Code, for example, has eight-week boot camps that teach middle and high school girls programming skills – in languages like Java, PHP, and Python – as well as &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt;, Web design, robotics, and mobile app development.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Computing Education Blog</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Mark Guzdial</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 06:30:36 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borgs&amp;#39; Stellar Work Reaps Its Due Reward - Inside &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; - TechNet &lt;b&gt;Blogs&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://blogs.technet.com/b/inside_microsoft_research/archive/2013/11/25/borgs-stellar-work-reaps-its-due-reward.aspx</link>
      <description>Inside Microsoft Research is a &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; from Microsoft Research that discusses the computing research projects and &lt;em&gt;computer-science&lt;/em&gt; technologies developed by our researchers in 13 labs around the world. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; “from problems in biology concerning patient-specific pathways in cancer—a research area that hopes eventually to lead to what the press calls &amp;#39;personalized medicine&amp;#39;—via problems involving network &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt; for huge graphs where even &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt; linear in the input are too&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Inside Microsoft Research</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Inside Microsoft Research</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 18:00:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One interesting thing: Average polynomial time &lt;b&gt;algorithms&lt;/b&gt; | Quasi &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://abagoffruit.wordpress.com/2013/11/24/one-interesting-thing-average-polynomial-time-algorithms/</link>
      <description>The most celebrated problem in theoretical &lt;em&gt;computer science&lt;/em&gt; is undoubtedly the P vs. NP problem. Let me explain what it is asking. (If you already know this, &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; If I ask you to factor 51445627, you are unlikely to be able to do that quickly ( although there are some very clever &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt; for doing it). But if I tell you that the prime factors are 5689 and 9043, then you can &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; This &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; is a catalogue of some of my thoughts. I write them down so that I understand them better. But sometimes&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Quasi-Coherent</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Simon</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 22:07:13 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do we need to be more tech savvy? | Strategically Communicating</title>
      <link>http://strategicallycommunicating.com/2013/11/25/do-we-need-to-be-more-tech-savvy/</link>
      <description>Any grounding in &lt;em&gt;computer science&lt;/em&gt; will introduce the learner to the use of &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt;. Though it has many formal definitions, an &lt;em&gt;algorithm&lt;/em&gt; is basically a recipe: a step-by-step process that results in a specified output. As such, it represents a structured approach to problem-solving that can be applied to &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Enter your email address to subscribe to this &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; and receive notifications of new posts by email. Join 75 other followers. &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt; at WordPress.com. | Customized Ocean Mist Theme.</description>
      <dc:publisher>Strategically Communicating</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>swhee1er</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 15:34:56 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Someone Let the American Studies Association Know It Got &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://chronicle.com/blogs/conversation/2013/11/25/will-someone-let-the-american-studies-association-know-it-got-hacked/</link>
      <description>&lt;em&gt;Computer Science&lt;/em&gt;/cyber Security Faculty. Dakota State University &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; It&amp;#39;s as if the tweets were generated by some &lt;em&gt;algorithm&lt;/em&gt; that translates banality into jargon! Again, very funny, but if I were a &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; Even the historian Claire Potter, whose Tenured Radical &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; is hosted on The Chronicle&amp;#39;s website, was taken in by the impression, generated by the fake Twitter discussion, that “discussion on Israeli [occupation] … has completely taken over” the conference. The conceit here was that the&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>The ConversationThe Conversation - Blogs - The Chronicle of Higher Education</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Jonathan Marks</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 20:42:46 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theory Announcements: [DMANET] SSTiC 2014: 1st announcement</title>
      <link>http://dmatheorynet.blogspot.com/2013/11/dmanet-sstic-2014-1st-announcement.html</link>
      <description>of &lt;em&gt;computer science&lt;/em&gt;. They will surely find it fruitful to listen and discuss with scholars who are main references in computing nowadays. REGIME: In addition to keynotes, 3 parallel sessions will be held during the whole event. Participants will be able to freely choose the courses they will be willing to attend as well as to move from one to another. VENUE: &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; Search This &lt;em&gt;Blog&lt;/em&gt;. Loading. &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt; [DMANET] Postdoc positions in &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt; and compl... [DMANET] 3 post-doc positions in&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Theory Announcements</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Lance Fortnow</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 11:25:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JMIR--Correlation and Interaction Visualization of Altmetric &lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://www.jmir.org/2013/11/e259/</link>
      <description>2Information Management Department, School of &lt;em&gt;Computer Science&lt;/em&gt; and Information Technology, Northeast Normal University, Changchun, Jilin, China 3Department of Social Medicine, &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; For example, Yan and Gerstein [16] examined the correlation between 18 different metrics, including article usage (HTML views, PDF downloads, XML downloads), citation statistics, &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; coverage, social bookmarking, and online ratings in the PLOS Article-Level Metrics. They observed that the &amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Journal of Medical Internet Research</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Ji Jun Guo</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 14:51:09 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSI Confusion: Remember the Mechanism! | Uncommon Descent</title>
      <link>http://www.uncommondescent.com/computer-science/csi-confusion-remember-the-mechanism/</link>
      <description>With that in mind, let&amp;#39;s consider a comment from a recent &lt;em&gt;blog&lt;/em&gt; post: For that matter &lt;b&gt;.....&lt;/b&gt; To model conservation of information we&amp;#39;d have to say something like &lt;em&gt;algorithmic&lt;/em&gt; information remains conserved, but not the Shannon entropy. If were to&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Uncommon Descent</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Winston Ewert</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 20:52:19 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Ways Coding Teaches Math - Probably Overthinking It - &lt;b&gt;Blogger&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>http://allendowney.blogspot.com/2013/11/six-ways-coding-teaches-math.html</link>
      <description>This is probably the most obvious of the six, but students can learn computational mechanisms and &lt;em&gt;algorithms&lt;/em&gt; by translating them into code from English, or from math notation, or even from another programming language. Any misunderstandings will be reflected in their code, so when they debug programs, they are also &lt;b&gt;....&lt;/b&gt; About Me. My Photo &amp;middot; Allen Downey. I am a Professor of &lt;em&gt;Computer Science&lt;/em&gt; at Olin College and a former Visiting Scientist at Google. View my complete profile&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;...&lt;/b&gt;</description>
      <dc:publisher>Probably Overthinking It</dc:publisher>
      <dc:creator>Allen Downey</dc:creator>
      <dc:date>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 19:41:00 GMT</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>